# KUMAR KARTIKEYA

Portfolio - <a href="https://portfolio-kumarkartikeya.vercel.app/">https://portfolio-kumarkartikeya.vercel.app/</a> kartikeyakumar1998@gmail.com 9990891253 Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh

### Summary

I'm a .NET developer with 2 years and 4 months of experience building applications using ASP.NET Core, WPF, SQL Server, and Web Applications. I focus on delivering user-friendly solutions and optimizing performance. I would like to implement my innovative ideas, skills and creativity for accomplishing the projects.

#### Skills

JAVA, C#, .Net Core, Asp.Net MVC5, Asp.Net WPF, WebAPI, .NET Framework, SQL Server 2019, MySQL 8.0, GIT, GitHub, JIRA, Javascript, Html5, CSS, TailwindCSS,

## Experience

Define Labs:

**Greater Noida. Uttar Pradesh** 

Software Developer

May 2022 - Present

Tech Stack: C#, .Net Core with C# WebAPI, ASP.Net, WPF, SQL Server 2019, GIT, JIRA

- Working on a Project CLUB CADDIE GOLF MANAGEMENT SOLUTION which is Developed in C#, PHP, and Asp.Net languages .
- Develop and maintain tee-time booking service, payments and refunds, book tee times, inventory management, payroll reports, membership billing reports, manage roles, punch cards, banner management.
- Extensive experience in design and development of applications using .Net and web technologies like bootstrap XML, CSS, Ajax, Web API and HTML and Windows technologies like WPF, WCF etc.
- Basic knowledge of MVC and Angular 4.
- Club Caddie builds cost-effective, cloud-based, and simple to use course management software and Retail POS System.
- Update or Create new UI Designs, ViewModel, Api and Controllers based on Task needs.
- Excellent code review and code debugging skills

#### Maowell Electronics Pvt.Ltd:

**Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh** 

**Production Line Leader** 

January 2020 - March 2020

Working as a Line Leader in Maowell Electronics Pvt.Ltd which makes USB wire and Charger for OPPO.

#### Lemon Electronics Pvt.Ltd:

**Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh** 

**Graduate Engineer Trainee** 

January 2018 - July 2018

Worked as Graduate Engineer Trainee for Assembling Keypad and smartphones.

#### Certificates

- Certificate of Completion in Core Java by INCAPP
- Certificate of Completion in WPF in C# by Udemy.
- Certificate Completion in Web Design(HTML, CSS, JS) by Udemy.

#### Education

Accurate Institute Of Management And Technology: Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh

Electronics and Communication Engineer 2014 - 2018

Percentage - 68

Udai Pratap Public School : Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh

Intermediate March 2014

**GPA - 68%** 

# **Personal Information**

Date of birth - 5 jun 1998

Marital status - Unmarried

Nationality - Indian

Hobbies - Playing cricket & volleyball, workout in gym